<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Danielkvist, Front-End Developer</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Danielkvist, Front-End Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© 2020 - Daniel (Danielkvist). Made with &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34; alt=&#34;Hugo&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danielkvist/hugo-tania-theme&#34; alt=&#34;Tania&#34;&gt;Tania&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.netlify.com/&#34; alt=&#34;Netlify&#34;&gt;Netlify&lt;/a&gt;.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Tania Tania is a simple and clean theme for Hugo, the framework for building static websites. Even though it&amp;rsquo;s still on development you can see it working right here, as it is the current theme I am using for my webpage.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t use any CSS framework like Bootstrap or Bulma since the goal is to create a theme as light as possible. Only basics CSS properties like CSS Grid and CSS Flexbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/education/</guid>
      <description>Education As a self-taught developer most of my education is based on Moocs, online courses, books and tutorials.
Moocs I have successfully completed MOOCs such as CS50&amp;rsquo;s - Introduction to Computer Science and CS50&amp;rsquo;s - Web Programming with Python and JavaScript and audited others like W3Cx - Introduction to Web Accessibility or CS50&amp;rsquo;s - Mobile App Development with React Native. Mentioning only the most recents.
Courses I have taken courses on platforms such as freeCodeCamp, Pluralsight, Frontend Master or Udemy about subjects like modern JavaScript, React, Golang, TDD, gRPC, Microservices, PostgreSQL, API design and Docker.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>