<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>misc on Dkvist</title>
    <link>/tags/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in misc on Dkvist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How can I improve my coding skills out of my code</title>
      <link>/posts/how-can-i-improve-out-of-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-can-i-improve-out-of-code/</guid>
      <description>Where this post came from The other day I was training with a friend of mine who in his free time tries to learn how to program that asked me if I could help him to improve his workflow when it comes to learn and to write code.
At first, frankly, I thought I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much to advice him. Basically because my own workflow is very far from perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming back to Windows 10 after 5 years using Linux to discover Chocolatey</title>
      <link>/posts/chocolatey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/chocolatey/</guid>
      <description>5 Years using Linux I started using Linux more than 5 years ago. In fact, my first distribution was Ubuntu 10.10. Ubuntu version on which Unity debuted for the first time (a GUI that I&amp;rsquo;ll never forget, though that&amp;rsquo;s another topic). But at that time I was still using Windows 7 along with Ubuntu. So I don&amp;rsquo;t really consider it a jump.
It was a couple of years later when I decided to use only Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world</title>
      <link>/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Who I am Well, the truth is, I&amp;rsquo;m a person who doesn&amp;rsquo;t like to repeat myself too much. So I&amp;rsquo;ll leave here the link to the page where I have already written about who I am.
What I am going to talk about I&amp;rsquo;m going to write about almost everything. But above all, about software development, Go and myself. I know it doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound very interesting or very original. But well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t say it&amp;rsquo;s going to be either.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>